konnektive.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy Policy - KonnektiveKonnektive

_**What does this privacy policy cover?**_

_**What information do we collect about you and how did we get that information?**_

_**How do we use the information we collect about you?**_

_**Do we share your personal information?**_

_**Is my personal information secure?**_

_**Where do you store my personal information?**_

_**How long will you keep my personal information? **_

_**Will you transfer my personal information across national borders?**_

_**What access do I have to the personal information that you collect? **_

_**Will you market products or services to me?**_

_**What if I have a dispute about how you handle my personal information? **_

_**Will this privacy policy change?**_

_**Contacting us**_

_**What does this privacy policy cover?**_

This privacy policy describes the privacy practices of Konnektive LLC’s websites that include a link to this policy. We want to help you understand how we collect and use the information you provide when you use,

  1. Our publicly available websites
  2. The Konnektive Mobile and other add-on applications, or apps
    * Konnektive Mobile for iOS®, and
    * Konnektive Mobile for Android™

_**What information do we collect about you and how did we get that information?**_

When you visit one of our web pages, create an account with us, enter a sweepstakes or contest, download one of our apps or e-books, post materials on one of our chat rooms or bulletin board, or contact us for support or other offerings, we collect information that identifies you. This includes information such as your name, contact information, and payment information. We may also sometimes collect other information that does not identify you, such as information on people’s visits and activity on our websites. We provide more detail in the list below.

  * **Contact Information** : If you are a customer of our services, we will collect general contact information that you provide to us. This includes: your name, shipping address, email address, telephone number and, where applicable, your company name. 
  * **Payment Information** : When we provided a fee-based service for you, we will collect the following information that you provide to us: billing address and credit card information.
  * **Login Information** : If you are a member or customer or our services, we will collect your user id (e-mail address) and password. 
  * **Online Identifiers** : When you access our web pages, we obtain your [Internet Protocol address](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IP_address), [browser user agent](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/User_agent), and your device id. 
  * **Data Trackers, Including[Cookies](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) and [Web Beacons](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_beacon)**: We collect information on
    * what pages you access or visit;
    * user-specific information on what pages you access or visit;
    * information you volunteer, such as survey information and/or site registrations;
    * bandwidth use;
    * referral source; 
    * operating system; 
    * mobile carrier (where applicable); and
    * system and connection performance.
  * **App-specific Information** : When you download and use our apps, we may also collect additional information about your mobile device, including the hardware model, operating system and version, mobile network information and time zone.

_**How do we use the information we collect about you?**_

We use contact information, including email addresses, to communicate with you if you are a customer of our services. This helps us to carry out the services you request from us and to notify you about updates to our web pages, products and policies, and marketing releases. When you subscribe to our fee-based services, we use this contact information, as well as payment information, for billing purposes and to carry out your requested services. 

Online identifiers, login information and data trackers are used to secure the limited access portions of our web pages and services. Data trackers help our web pages work. They also help us to improve our content and to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor. In addition, online identifiers and data trackers to prevent and reduce fraudulent practices. For more information about our use of cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies, please read  “ _More Information On Data Trackers_ ” below.

_**More Information On Data Trackers**_ **:**

**Cookies** are small text files that are stored by your web browser when you use websites. When you visit our web pages, our web server sends a cookie to your computer. You can control how websites use cookies by configuring your browser’s privacy settings (please refer to your browser’s help function to learn more about cookie controls). Note that if you disable cookies entirely, our web pages may not function properly. We use cookies in several ways, such as:

  * To show whether you have visited a web page previously;
  * To store your preferences; 
  * To show how you navigate around a web page and the most commonly clicked links on a specific web page; 
  * To gather certain technical information, such as your browser version and operating system; and
  * To estimate and report how many different users are on our web sites. 

This allows us to make your experience on our web site simple and meaningful, to customize web page content, to alert you to new areas that we think might interest you, to provide better services, and to ensure that you are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, when you return to our web pages. It also helps us to conduct research to improve the content and services of our web sites.

**Web beacons** (sometimes called “tracking pixels”, “transparent GIFs”, “clear GIFs”, “pixel gifs”, or “pixel tags”) are **** tiny, invisible images that are embedded on web pages and emails and are stored on a your hard drive. They help us to count users who visit our web sites or open our emails. Tracking pixels help us figure out if certain features, notifications, and products or services are effective and if they can be improved.  You can modify your browser settings to control web beacons.

**Third-Party Cookies  
**We may also from time to time engage third parties to track and analyze data and statistics that do not identify you. This practice helps us administer our websites and improve their quality. These third parties may use cookies and web beacons to help track visitor behavior. Their cookies and web beacons may track how you interact with a web site through the use of cookies and the data collected may include how you navigate around a web page and the most commonly clicked links on a specific web page. They may also collect technical information, such as your browser version and operating system. If collected, this information will be used by us to evaluate and, if necessary, modify our website to improve the functions and make it easier for customers to use. Your name and contact information is not collected or used for this purpose.

As a part of our efforts to carry out and improve our services to you and to monitor and improve the functions of our websites, we may also undertake profiling or automated individual decision-making. Automated individual decision-making refers to a decision made solely on the basis of automated processing of your personal data, without human involvement. For instance, we may process personal information using an algorithm or a software code. Profiling is automated processing of personal data to evaluate certain information collected about an individual. We conduct profiling and automated decision-making to better understand your interests and preferences and to adapt our communications to your user profile. You can address any questions or concerns about this practice by _contacting us_. 

_**Do we share your personal information?**_

Konnektive works with companies that help us run our business. From time to time, we need to share some of your personal information with these companies so that they can perform requested services. They can only access your personal information to carry out the tasks we have asked them to do. They are required to hold this information in confidence. And they must meet both legal and industry standards to ensure that your data is protected. We may share your personal information with _service providers_ , _affiliates_ , _business partners_ , or other _third parties_.

_**Service Providers**_

Konnektive may share information about our visitors and/or customers with our contracted service providers so that these service providers can provide services on our behalf. 

  * We work with companies who help us: host our services and data, manage how our services function, host our customer relationship management, improve and automate our marketing techniques, incorporate customer service and other software platforms, process payments, collect delinquent accounts, fulfill, process and deliver orders, and market and promote our products and services, including by email.
  * These service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide the requested services to us.  Without limiting the foregoing, Konnektive may also share information about visitors, members, and/or customers with our service providers to ensure the quality of information provided. Without your permission, Konnektive does not share, sell, rent, or trade any information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

_**Affiliates**_ __

Konnektive may share information with affiliate companies in order to work with them.  For example, we may need to share personal information with other companies within our corporate family for customer support, marketing, technical operations and account management purposes.

_**Third Parties**_

We discussed in the section of the Privacy Statement, _What information do we collect about you and how did we get that information?,_ that we, or our advertisers, may collect information about you through cookies and web beacons. You can control this collection through your _web browser_.

  * We also work with partners to create programs that help you to get the most out of our services and provide you the opportunity to purchase complementary products and services that may be used in tandem with our services. 
  * We may disclose your information to one or more trusted partners so they can help you or offer you complementary or value-added products and services. In each case, the trusted partner will confirm they will (1) hold your information in confidence, and (2) not use it for any purpose except for the purposes described above. But will provide your personal information only with your prior consent.
  * We partner with third party ad networks to display advertising on our web pages or to manage our advertising on other websites. Our ad network partners may use _cookies and web beacons_ to collect information about your activities on our websites and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. To opt out of this type of cookies, visit the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. Even if you opt out through the NAI website, you can still receive communications you have signed up to receive from us unless you _opt out_ of these communications as well.

We may also share your personal information _to provide reviews or testimonials_ , _in case of a company sale or transfer_ , and if we are _compelled by law_ :

_**To Provide Reviews or Testimonials**_

We may select and post customer testimonials about our services, which may contain personal information such as your name and/or the city, state, or country in which you live. We will obtain your consent before we post any testimonial with your name. When you submit a review, you give us permission to post that review. If you post this content, it will be available to other users. Your posting may also become public and we cannot prevent that information from being used in a manner that may violate our privacy policy or the law. If you would like us to remove or delete your name, testimonial, or review from our web pages, please _contact us_. Note that copies of information that you have updated, modified, or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of our web pages for a period of time.

_**Company Sale or Transfer**_

Should we sell all or part of our business, the customer information that we have collected may be transferred along with the sale but the information will be treated in the same manner described here. In the event of any significant changes to the manner in which your information is handled, we will notify you.

_**Compelled Disclosure**_

Sometimes, we are required to use or disclose information provided if required by law or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the Konnektive’s rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

_**Is my personal information secure?**_

We use reasonable and diligent efforts to maintain accurate information on our customers and have adopted and implemented reasonable industry standard security procedures to protect any such information collected against the loss, misuse or alteration. We constantly monitor our systems, which are protected using industry-standard security measures. Although Konnektive will use reasonable efforts to secure network communications and our websites, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

**Public Disclosures Made by You**

If you use a bulletin board, blog, comment or discussion forum or chat room made available on one of our web pages, you should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages, and could be potentially searchable through search engines. We are not responsible for the potential misuse by third parties of any personal information that you choose to submit in these various forums.

**When You Use Widgets Listed on Our Web Pages**

A widget **** is a small application with limited functions. It can be installed and used within a web page. It occupies a portion of a webpage and does something useful with information fetched from other websites. We may provide widgets on our web pages so you can share information on third-party platforms. Our web pages may also include social media features, such as the Facebook® or Twitter® button and similar widgets and interactive mini-programs that run on our site. The companies running those widgets may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable their widget to function properly. Social media widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web pages. Since these other parties have their own privacy policies—and your use of their widgets is governed by their policies—we encourage you to review the privacy statements for the companies running those widgets.

**Third Party Sites**

Our Sites may contain links to third party websites. Please note that the privacy and other policies of any such third-party website may differ materially from this Policy. We strongly recommend that customers review the privacy policies of any such third party prior to submitting personally identifiable information. Konnektive has no control over and is not responsible for the information practices of other websites, including those to which we may link and those which may link to us.

_**Where do you store my personal information?**_

Your personal information and files are stored on Konnektive servers and the servers of companies we hire to provide services to us. Your personal information may be transferred across national borders because we have servers located worldwide and the companies we hire to help us run our business are located in different countries. 

_**How long will you keep my personal information?**_

We will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to provide you with the product and services you have requested and as needed to comply with our legal obligations and enforce our agreements.

_**Will you transfer my personal information across national borders?**_

We primarily store information about our visitors, members, and customers in the United States. However, we may transfer your personal information across national borders to other countries in compliance with applicable laws. If you are a European resident, we transfer your data based on one or more of the following legal mechanisms: Standard Contractual Clauses. 

_**What access do I have to the personal information that you collect?**_

Under the law of some countries, you have the right to: 

  * Access the personal information that you provide us and that we maintain;
  * Correct, update or delete that personal information that we no longer have business reasons for retaining;
  * Restrict processing while we review any concerns you may have over the accuracy of the personal information we maintain; 
  * Object to 
    * Data processing based upon legitimate interests,
    * Data processing for research or statistics,
    * Direct marketing, and
    * Decisions based exclusively on automated processing, such as profiling, so long as the decision does not impact our ability to enter or perform our contract services for you or is not based on your explicit consent;
  * Withdraw your consent in instances where we must have your consent to contact you; and
  * Transfer, or port, your personal information that you provided us in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format.

To review, correct, delete or otherwise modify this information, or to remove your email address from our marketing database, please email your request to [info@Konnektive.com](file:///C:/Users/Rachel/AppData/Local/Microsoft/Windows/INetCache/Content.Outlook/FVOO89EL/info@Konnektive.com) or otherwise review the “ _Contacting Us_ ” section beloww. Requests to access, change, or delete your information will be addressed within a reasonable timeframe and in all cases within 30 days.

To protect customer privacy and security, we reserve the right to take reasonable steps to verify your identity prior to granting access to or processing changes or corrections to such information. 

Please note that we need to retain certain information about you for legal and internal business reasons, such as fraud prevention. We will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to provide you the services you have requested and as needed to comply with our legal obligations and enforce our agreements.

_**What if I have a dispute about how you handle my personal information?**_

If you are an E.U. resident and you have a dispute about how we are handling your personal information, you have the right to complain to a supervisory authority to enforce your rights. You can contact Konnektive’s lead supervisory at: .

_**Will you market products or services to me?**_

Konnektive and companies we hire to help us market our web pages and services on our behalf may use your information to provide you with information and offers related to our services. You may decline to receive these offers by _contacting us_.

You may also opt out of receiving future promotional/marketing messages from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link found in the footer of our email messages. Please note that if you opt out of promotional/marketing messages, you may continue to receive certain communications from us, such as administrative and services announcements and/or messages about your account/profile.

_**Will this privacy policy change?**_

If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the changes to our Privacy Statement web page to notify you of these changes. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement for the latest information on our privacy practices.

_**Contacting Us**_

  * Legal /Privacy Compliance
  * Address: Konnektive LLC., 954 Ave Ponce de Leon #607, San Juan, PR 00917

  * Phone:1-800-270-8701
  * E-mail: [info@Konnektive.com](mailto:info@Konnektive.com) 

© 2018Konnektive LLC. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved by Konnektive.  
Konnektive is a registered trademark of Konnektive LLC. IOS is a registered trademark of Cisco Systems, Inc. Android is a trademark of Google Inc. Facebook is a registered trademark of Facebook, Inc. Twitter is a registered trademark of Twitter, Inc.
